HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Legislative Department Files
1967-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/001
9.5 cubic feet
9.5 linear ft.
Records.
5840643
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 31, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 AV: HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 MB: HERE Memorabilia 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/002: HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/003: HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf: HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files 6199/015: HERE Editor Files
Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Union; Hotel & Restaurant and Bartenders International Union
5840643
- Alaska Alliance, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- California State Council, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Florida State Council, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Illinois Legislative Papers, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Illinois State Council, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Indiana State Council, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Indiana State Council, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Massachusetts State Council, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minnesota State Council, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Missouri State Council, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Montana State Council, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Nevada Culinary Topics, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Scope and Contents
  Spring Issue
- Nevada State Council, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- New Jersey State Council, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- New Jersey, Culinary Conference, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- New York Culinary Workers, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- New York, Hotel and Restaurant Employees, State Legislature, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- New Jersey Culinary Workers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Oregon State Council, 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Washington Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Washington State Council, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Local 879 Fairbanks, Alaska, 1978-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local No. 2, California, 1977-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Local No. 2 San Francisco, California, 1976-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Local 11 Los Angeles, California, 1977-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- San Jose, California Culinary Workers, Newsprint, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Local 19, San Jose California, 1976-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 30, San Diego, California, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Local 309 Palm Springs, California, 1975-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Local 62 Fresno, California, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Local 309 Palm Springs, California, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Local 483 Monterey, California, 1976-1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Monterey, California Newsprint, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Local 498 Santa Barbara, California, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Local 531 Pasadena, California, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Local 535 Riverside, California, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Local 681 Long Beach, California, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Santa Barbara County, California, Newsprint (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Local 703 Santa Maria, California, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Local 814 Santa Monica, California, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Santa Rosa, California, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Local 40 Vancouver, B.C. and Vicinity, Canada, 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Local 14 Denver, Colorado, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Local 35 New Haven, Connecticut, 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Local 217 New Haven-Providence, Rhode Island, 1979-1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Delaware Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Local 25, Washington, DC, 1979-1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Washington, DC Culinary Employees, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Romeo and Juliet Restaurant, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Colonial Williamsburg Workers Strike, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Local 32, Washington, DC, 1990-2000 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- US House of Representatives Rest Organizing Cafeteria Workers, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Local No. 25 Hotel and Restaurant Employees Washington, DC, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  The Hotel Association of Washington, DC
- Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Restricted
- Local 104, Tampa, Florida, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Local 355 Greater Miami Area and Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1977-1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Local 737 Orlando, Florida, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Hawaii Newsprint, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Local 5 Honolulu, Hawaii, 1976-1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Contains one photograph
- State of Illinois, General Assembly, 1979-1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Local 1 Chicago, Illinois, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Local 15 Southern, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Local 16 Peoria, Illinois, 1980-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Local 117 Belleville, Illinois, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Local 43 Chicago, Illinois, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Illinois, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Local 450Berwyn, Illinois, Forest Park, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Local 166 New Orleans, Louisiana, 1977-1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- New Orleans, Louisiana, Hyatt Hotel, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 7 Baltimore, Maryland, 1975-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Local 26 Boston, Massachusetts, 1977-1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Boston Local 26 Newsprint, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Local 29 Lawrence, Massachusetts, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Western Massachusetts, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Local 17 Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota, 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Michigan Local 24, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Local 21 Rochester, Minnesota, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Local 427 Missoula, Montana, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Local 56, Billings, Montana, 1976-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Local 427 Missoula, Montana, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Las Vegas, Nevada, 1977-1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Local 86 Reno, Nevada, 1980-1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Las Vegas, Nevada Newsprint, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  March 9 1992
- Local 226 Las Vegas, Nevada, 1978-1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Local 165 Las Vegas, Nevada, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Frontier Hotel, Las Vegas, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- New Jersey, 1973-1987 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Local 54 Atlantic City, NJ, 1974-1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Newark, New Jersey, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Gambling, New Jersey, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Local 4 Buffalo, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Buffalo, New York, Newsprint, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Local 6 New York, 1977-1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Buffalo, New York, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Local 37 Jamaica, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Local 69 New York and Vicinity, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Local 76 Monticello, NY, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Local 100 New York, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Local 15 Syracuse NY, 1981-1993 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Local 471 Albany, NY, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Local 36 Raleigh, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Local 10 Cleveland, Ohio, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Oregon-Portland, Salem Newsprint, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Local 9 Portland and Salem, Oregon, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Pennsylvania Travel Industry, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Local 274 Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1981-1991 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Local 301 Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1981-1992 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  Contains a photograph
- Local 610, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico, 1974-1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  In Spanish and English
- Local 217 Rhode Island, 1980-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Local 270 Myrtle Beach, South Carolina, 1977-1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Virginia AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Local 8 Seattle and Renton, Washington, 1976-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Contains 5 photographs
- Local 20 Tacoma, Pierce and Bremerton Kitsap Counties, Washington, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Wenatchee, Washington, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Letter to Senate Finance Committee re: Business Deductibility (full), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  April 10 1986
- Letters to Members of Ways and Means and Finance, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  April
- Congressional Responses to April Letters to Finance and Ways and Means Members, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Follow-up Letter to April, 1985 Letter on Business Entertainment Expense Deduction to HS Ways and Means and Finance (Box 5, Folder 4)
  June 1985
- Budget Clippings Folder 1, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Budget Clippings Folder 2, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Budget Clippings Folder 3, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Budget Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Business Meal 1986 Clippings (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Commerce-Product Liability Bills, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Commerce-Product Liability Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Commerce-Product Liability Testimony, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Congressional Responses to June, 1985 Letter re: 3 Martini Lunches (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Correspondence D.A.T.O., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Drinking Age, Dram Shops Clippings, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Drinking Age, Drinking Age Clippings, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Drinking Age, Drinking Age Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Drinking Age, MADD Clippings, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Drinking Age, MADD Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Energy Folder 1, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Energy Folder 2, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Energy-Excise Tax Clippings (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Energy-Voting Record, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Energy-Weekend Closing Clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Energy-Weekend Closing Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Energy Rationing Clippings, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Gaming, Nevada Bills, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Nevada Gaming Clippings, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Nevada Gaming Correspondence, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- New Jersey Gaming Clippings, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Labor-ERISA Bills, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Labor-ERISA Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- ERISA Fact Sheets, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Health, Welfare and Pension, ERISA, Support of HR Title IV, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  May 1 1980
- Health, Welfare and Pension, ERISA, Support of HR 3904 Title IV, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- HR 3904, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- ERISA, HR 3904, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- ERISA HR 3904 Responses, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- ERISA, News Articles, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- ERISAS 1076 Letters to Senate, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- ERISA S 1076 Responses, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Labor ERISA Responses, S 1076, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- ISTEA Funding, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Judiciary Bankruptcy Newspaper Clippings, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Judiciary Immigration, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Judiciary Immigration Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Judiciary Immigration Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Judiciary Immigration Correspondence, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Judiciary Visa Waiver Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Judiciary US Customs Correspondence, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Labor, Business Lunches, Clippings, 1973-1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Labor, Business Lunches, Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Labor, Business Lunches, Testimony, 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Labor, General Clippings, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Labor, General, Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Labor, Labor Law Reform Bills, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Labor, Labor Law Reform, Clippings, 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Labor, Labor Law Reforms, Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Labor, Labor Law Reform, Testimony, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Labor, Labor Racketeering, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Labor, Labor Racketeering, Congressional Records, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Labor, Labor Racketeering, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Minimum Wage, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Minimum Wage Bill Letter, REJ, Labor and Human Resources Committee, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  June 21 1988
- Labor, Minimum Wage, Clippings, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Minimum Wage Commission, 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Press Releases, Bulletins and Minimum Wage, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Labor, NLRB/Wagner Act, Clippings, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Labor, NLRB/Wagner Act, Congressional Records, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Labor, Polygraphs Folder 1, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Labor, Polygraphs Folder 2, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Labor, Polygraphs Folder 3, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Labor, Polygraphs Folder 4, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Labor, Polygraphs, Bills, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Labor, Polygraphs, Clippings, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Labor, Polygraphs, Congressional Record, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Labor, Polygraphs, Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Labor, Minimum Wage, Bills, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Labor, Subminimum Wage, Clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Labor, Subminimum Wage, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Labor, Subminimum Wage, Testimony, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Letter to Congress re: Tax Bill and Follow-up Responses, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  December 3 1985
- Taxes, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Tax, Foreign Conventions, Bills, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Tax, Foreign Conventions, Clippings, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Tax, Fringe Benefits/Airlines, Bills, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Tax, Fringe Benefits/Airlines, Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Tax, Fringe Benefits/Cars, Clippings, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Tax, Fringe Benefits/Cars, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Tax, Fringe Benefits/Cars, Testimony, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Tax, Fringe Benefits/VEBA, Clippings, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Tax, Fringe Benefits/VEBA, Testimony, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Tax Reform Folder 1, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Tax Reform Folder 2, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Tax Reform Folder 3, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Tax Reform Folder 4, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Tax Reform Folder 5, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Tax Reform, 1986 Congressional Record (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Tax Reform, 1986 Senate Releases, Statements (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Tax Reform Bill, Laxalt-Inouye Amendment Business Meals (Senate Letters), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  June 12 1986
- Tax Reform, Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Summary of Senate Finance Committee Staff Option for Comprehensive Tax Reform, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Tax Simplification Bills, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Tax Simplification Clippings Folder 1, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Tax Simplification Clippings Folder 2, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Tax Simplification Clippings Folder 3, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Tax Simplification Clippings Folder 4, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Tax Simplification, Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Tax Simplification, Testimony, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  April and June 1985
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 1, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 2, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 3, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 4, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 5, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 6, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 7, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Folder 8, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, HR Bills, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Canada, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Quebec Tipping Legislation
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Clippings, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Tip Reporting, Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Tip Reporting, Senate Testimony, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Tax, Tip Reporting, Testimony, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Contains French and English
- Tobacco, Preventing Addiction to Smoking Among Teens Act, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union Legislative Conference, Washington Court Hotel, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  May 16 2000 - May 19 2000
- JAL/Nikko Hotel, Morty Miller REJ and Paul Clifford, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- JAL/Nikko Hotel, Morty Miller REJ and Paul Clifford, Folder 2, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Nikko, Japanese Hotels, California, 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Nikko, Japanese Hotels, California, Folder 2, 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Nikko, Japanese Hotels, California, Folder 3, 1985-1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Las Vegas Strike, Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- New York City Strike, Hotel Employees, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Old Correspondence, US Congress and Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Fact Sheets for Travel and Tourism Government Affairs Council, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Bills and Papers on Tourism Policy, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Tourism and Travel, Congressional Record and Clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Trade, Senate Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Trade, Newspaper Clippings, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- US Department of Commerce, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- US Department of Labor Miscellaneous Documents, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- The Office of Congressional and Intergovernmental Affairs, Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Senate Finance Committee, Legitimate Business Meal and Entertainment Expense Deduction (HEREIU-REJ), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  April 29 1993
- Matthew Walker Testimony, Travel Tourism in America Today, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Subcommittee on Commerce, Trade and Consumer Protection; House Committee on Energy; April 30 2003
- Subcommittee on Employer/Employee Relations of the US House of Representatives, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  July 1999
- Subcommittee on Consumer Affairs, Foreign Commerce and Tourism of the US Senate Committee on Commerce, Science and Transportation, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  October 12 2001
- Robert E Juliano Testimony, Legitimate Business Meal and Entertainment Expense Deduction, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  House Ways and Means Committee; March 31 1993
- Testimony on Social Security Tax Treatment on Cash Tips, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Subcommittee on Social Security; July 24 1990
- Tourism Testimony, HR 4369, S1791, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  House Subcommittee on Transportation and Hazardous Materials; May 23 1990
- Subcommittee on labor Standards, HR 1834, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  February 23 1988
- The Minimum Wage Restoration Act of 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  July 30 1987
- The Minimum Wage Restoration Act of 1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Chairman Robert Packwood, Business Lunches, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Senate Finance Committee; October 4 1985
- REJ, Tax Proposals to the Congress for Fairness, Growth and Simplicity, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Ways and Means Committee; June 12 1985
- Hearings on HR 907, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  October 3 1984
- S 2520, Appropriations for Travel and Tourism, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  April 6 1984
- Subcommittee on Business Trade and Tourism, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  March 2 1983
- Statement of Robert Juliano (HEREIU) before the IRS, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  Tip-reporting regulations; February 8 1983
- HR 6300 Taxpayer Compliance Act, Daniel Rostenkowski, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  House Ways and Means Committee, May 18 1982
- Testimony regarding Taxpayer Compliance Improvement Act, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  Senate Committee on Finance, Subcommittee on IRS Oversight; March 22 1982
- HR 4592, Testimonies of Robert Juliano and Pete Stark, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures; March 16 1982
- Subminimum Wage S 348, S 430, S 658, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources; March 25 1981
- Testimony for Foreign Convention Supporting HR 7566, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Ways and Means Committee; September 18 1980
- Tourism, S 2248, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  Senate Committee on Commerce, Science and Transportation; March 5 1980
- Testimony of Senator DK Inouye, Chairman regarding Energy Bill, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  Senate Subcommittee on Merchant marine and Tourism
- Testimony regarding the National Tourism Policy Act S 1097, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  Subcommittee on Transportation and Commerce; July 24 1979
- Testimony regarding Foreign Convention, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  US Senate Committee on Finance, Subcommittee on Tourism and Sugar; July 20 1970
- Testimony before Senate Subcommittee on Finance, S 1674, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Testimony Senator Dan Inouye, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  Subcommittee on Merchant Marine and Tourism; February 26 1979
- Testimony of Honorable James Florio, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  Subcommittee on Transportation and Commerce; March 15 1979
- Testimony regarding President Carter's Tax Proposals, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  March 20 1978
- Committee on Finance, S 1674, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  July 24 1978
- Testimony regarding Revenue Act of 1978, HR 13511 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  Senate Subcommittee on Finance; August 23 1978
- Testimony of Senator Dan Inouye, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Senate Subcommittee on Merchant, Marine and Tourism' September 20 1978
- Testimony before the Subcommittee of the Senate Labor and Public Affairs, S 1871, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  August 4 1977
- Testimony of Russell B Long, Chairman, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  Senate Finance Committee; July 22 1976
- HR 6715 Technical Corrections Act, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  Committee on Ways and Means, September 8 1977
- HR 9281, Ways and Means Committee, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  October 6 1977
- Testimony before Senate Subcommittee on Foreign Commerce, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  April 21 1976
- Testimony before House Subcommittee on Transportation and Commerce, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  March 19 1975
- Testimony before the Subcommittee on Census and Population, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  April 14 1975
- Testimony before the Senate Subcommittee on Foreign Commerce and Tourism, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  September 29 1975
- Testimony before Subcommittee on Labor Standards, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  October 22 1976
- Testimony before Senate Subcommittee on Foreign Commerce and Tourism, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  March 29 1974
- Testimony before Senate Subcommittee on Foreign Commerce and Tourism, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  April 26 1974
- Testimony for the Committee on the Holidays and Celebrations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  July 11 1974